Fight to survive.
Prisoner of War is a action, war, thriller film directed by Louis Mandylor.
British RAF Wing Commander James Wright is captured by the Japanese during
WWII and forced to fight in brutal hand-to-hand combat.
The Japanese soldiers get more than they bargained for when Wright’s years of
martial arts training in Hong Kong prove him to be a formidable opponent.
Wing Commander James Wright, played by Scott Adkins.
Lt. Col. Benjiro Ito, played by Peter Shinkoda.
Sgt. Gabriel Villanueva, played by Michael Copon.
Theresa, played by Gabbi Garcia.
The Beard, played by Michael Rene Walton.
Captain Endo, played by Masanori Mimoto.
Prisoner of War (formerly titled Death March) is a 2025  martial arts war film directed by
Louis Mandylor and written by Marc Clebanoff, based on a story by Scott Adkins.
The film features Adkins alongside Peter Shinkoda, Donald
Cerrone, Michael Copon, and Gabbi Garcia.
Produced by Odyssey Motion Pictures and distributed by Well Go USA Entertainment, it
combines martial arts action with a World War II prisoner-of-war narrative.
It premiered at the Beverly Hills Film Festival in April 2025 and had a limited
theatrical and digital release in the United States on September 19, 2025.
Set during the Battle of Bataan, the plot centers on British RAF officer Wing Commander James Wright
(Adkins), who is captured by Japanese forces and confined to a harsh POW camp in the Philippines.
There, Wright is forced into hand-to-hand combat
matches for his captors’ amusement.
Using his prior martial arts training, he motivates resistance among
fellow prisoners while devising a bold escape plan.
The film received mixed to positive critical feedback, with praise for Adkins’s performance and the
fight choreography, though the narrative depth and supporting characters faced criticism.
Reviewers highlighted its fusion of war epic and martial arts elements,
with some calling it a raw, visceral take on the genre.
The film explores themes of world war ii, prisoner
of war, internment camp, 1940s.
The tone is dark and intense.